castlegem.co.uk 2011-06-13

# Castlegem - Privacy Statement

### Castlegem Ltd. Statement of Privacy

##### Last updated: April 16th, 2008

We are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete Castlegem Ltd. privacy statement.

### Collecting your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when purchasing Castlegem Ltd. products or contacting Castlegem Ltd. Personal information collected by Castlegem Ltd. often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This information is kept offsite. 

### Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for three primary purposes:

###### To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.

###### To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.

###### To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Castlegem Ltd.

Castlegem Ltd. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Castlegem Ltd. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Castlegem Ltd., and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of customers of Castlegem Ltd., its Web sites, or the public.

### Control of your Personal Information

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Castlegem Ltd. will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

Castlegem Ltd. may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service issues related to a product or service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

### Access to your Personal Information

You may request to review your personal information on file with us at any time, and may update this information at any time.

### Security of your Personal Information

Castlegem Ltd. strictly protects the security of your personal information and honours your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the UK or any other country where Castlegem Ltd, its subsidiaries, affiliates, or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

### Use of Cookies

To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, Castlegem Ltd. collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the site.

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.

### Changes to this Statement

Castlegem Ltd. will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the .last updated. date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, Castlegem Ltd. will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

Castlegem Ltd.  
Office 404, 4th floor, Albany House  
324/326 Regent St.  
London  
W1B 3HH  
UK
